Finding aid for Media Resources Center (University of Michigan) Films and Videotapes, 1930s and 1948-1987
Bentley Historical Library
- Series B, Understanding Our World
  - African Development, 1960-1961; [851831-B-95]; (Ambassador Halm of Ghana and Michigan Gov. G. Mennen Williams discuss African problems and potentials on show hosted by Detroit City Councilman William Patrick Jr. Features: G. Mennen Williams; W.M.Q. Halm; William T. Patrick, Jr.)
    - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #284, Pos. #515
    - Streaming File:, 851831-B95.flv
  - Program for the Aged: Sen Wayne Morse, 1960-1961; [851831-B-96]; (U.S. Senator Wayne Morse discusses the problems of health care for the aged and expansion of social security benefits. Features: Woodrow Hunter, UM-Geron.; Sen. Wayne Morse; Clark Tibbits, HEW)
    - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #289, Pos. #522
  - Search for Industry, The, 1960-1961; [851831-B-97]; (Representatives of industry, labor, and government discuss how the citizens of Michigan seek to create new jobs. Features: Gardner Ackley, UM-Econ.)
    - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #292, Pos. #701
    - Streaming File:, 851831-B97.flv
  - Profile of a Music Pioneer, 1960-1961; [851831-B-98]; (Mukle, world renowned cellist and one of the first women to make a career as concert artist, discusses the struggles of women musicians in the Victorian Age, her association with suffragist Emmeline Pankhurst, and plays several selections. Features: Oliver Edel, UM-Music; Muy Mukle)
    - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #293, Pos. #706
  - Frontiers of the Law, 1960-1961; [851831-B-99]; (The education a student receives at UM Law school is briefly sketched and then a federal judge, an English barrister, and a New York attorney discuss the difficult problems new lawyers will face in the next decade. Features: John Brown; Lord Hartley Shawcross; Ralph Carson)
    - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #297, Pos. #714
  - Music from the University of Michigan, 1960-1961; [851831-B-100]; (A final performance by the University of Michigan Symphony Band before their trip to Russia. Features: William D. Revelli, UM-Music; Symphony Band)
    - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #299, Pos. #711
  - Interview with Ayn Rand, An, 1961; [851831-B-101]; (Ayn Rand, noted novelist, philosopher, and controversial figure on the modern intellectual scene, offers her views on the current intellectual crisis in American society. Features: James Mc'Connell, UM-Psych.; Ayn Rand)
    - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #312, Pos. #739
    - Streaming File:
  - Changing Africa, 1961-1962; [851831-B-102]; (Assistant Secretary of State for African Affairs comments on U.S. policy toward African independence movements and on appeal of communist ideology in Africa. Features: G. Mennen Williams; Morris Bornstein, UM-Econ.)
    - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #338, Pos. #789
  - Schoolyards, Starlings and Scientists, 1961-1962; [851831-B-103]; (Three of the key health officials involved in unraveling the mystery of an outbreak of histoplasmosis in Milan, MI tell their story. Features: Horace Dodge, UM-Med.; Otto Engelke; John DeTar)
    - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #344, Pos. #769
  - Mountain Wolf Woman, 1961-1962; [851831-B-104]; (Story of Winnebago Indians is reflected in the life of Mountain Wolf Woman as told to a UM anthropologist who was adopted into the tribe. Features: Nancy O. Lurie, UM-Anthro.)
    - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #347, Pos. #771
  - Press Conference: Robert Oppenheimer, 1961-1962; [851831-B-105]; (World renowned nuclear physicist comments on disarmament, civil defense, and the future of science at a special news conference. Features: J. Robert Oppenheimer)
    - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #355, Pos. #776
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 8)
    - Streaming File:, 851831-B105.flv
  - Discovering Arithmetic: 4 + 4 = 13, 1961-1962; [851831-B-106]; (Professor Joseph Payne plays "Eskimo Arithmetic," counting in base five, with three youngsters and demonstrates new teaching methods emphasizing discovery over rote memorization. Features: Joseph Payne, UM-Ed.)
    - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #357, Pos. #755
  - Peace Corps, The, 1961-1962; [851831-B-107]; (Interview with Peace Corps Director Sargent Shriver, includes footage of John Kennedy's speech announcing Peace Corps and Shriver's talk to Corps volunteers trained at Michigan. Features: Sargent Shriver; Arthur Eastman, UM-Engl.)
    - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #359, Pos. #754
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 8)
    - Streaming File:, 851831-B107.flv
  - Group Worker, The, 1962; [851831-B-108]; (A documentary view of a twentieth century profession, the Group Worker examines this special type of social work. Features: Robert Vinter, UM-SW)
    - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #364, Pos. #3081
  - New Power: Nuclear Energy for Electricity, 1962; [851831-B-109]; (Four outstanding experts explore the rapidly developing field of nuclear-fueled power generation. Features: William Kerr, UM-Eng.; Samuel Estep, UM-Law; James Campbell; Robert Hartwell)
    - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #366, Pos. #744
  - What Shall It Profit? (Peace Corps), 1962; [851831-B-249]; (Film documentary of Peace Corps training program at the University of Michigan, and discussion by program leaders. Features: Robert Leetsma, UM-Ed.; Harold Dorr, UM)
    - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #377, Pos. #747
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 9)
    - Streaming File:, 851831-B249.flv
  - Freedom in Threatened Society, 1962; (Ten part program hosted by Hugh Fleetwood, UM-Phil.)
    - Freedom and National Security, 1962; [851831-B-110-1]; (In this part UM faculty and state legislator discuss the communist threat, government loyalty-security programs and their impact on civil liberties. Features: Gilbert Bursley; Sanford Kadish, UM-Law; John Searle, UM-Phil.; Stephen Tonsor, UM-Hist.)
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #375, Pos. #736
      - Use copy:, DVD (Box 9)
      - Streaming File:, 851831-B110-1.flv
    - Freedom, Loyalty and Subversion, 1962; [851831-B-110-2]; (In this part University of Michigan faculty members discuss the nature and meaning of loyalty and disloyalty in a democratic nation. Features: Jerold Israel, UM-Law; Elton McNeil, UM-Psych.; John Searle, UM-Phil.,Stephen Tonsor, Hist.)
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #378, Pos. #749
      - Use copy:, DVD (Box 9)
      - Streaming File:, 851831-B110-2.flv
    - Freedom and the Press, 1962; [851831-B-110-3]; (University of Michigan faculty members investigate the range of problems affecting the rights, liberties and duties of the free press in America. Features: Ben Yablonky, UM-Jour.; John Searle, UM-Phil.; Stephen Tonsor, UM-Hist; Jerold Israel, UM-Law)
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #379, Pos. #750
      - Use copy:, DVD (Box 9)
      - Streaming File:, 851831-B110-3.flv
    - Freedom and Religion, 1962; [851831-B-110-4]; (University of Michigan faculty members examine the issue of church and state and offer their views on the nature and meaning of religious liberty and democratic freedom of religious conscience and expression. Features: Sanford Kadish, UM-Law; Gerhard Lenski, UM-Soc.; John Searle, UM-Phil.; Stephen Tonsor)
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #380, Pos. #723
      - Use copy:, DVD (Box 9)
      - Streaming File:, 851831-B110-4.flv
    - Freedom and Labor, 1962; [851831-B-110-5]; (University of Michigan authorities discuss the civil rights and basic freedoms of the American worker and the responsibilities of government, management and labor unions. Features: Sanford Kadish, UM-Law; Jerold Israel, UM-Law; Stephen Tonsor, UM-Hist; Albert Steigerwalt)
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #384, Pos. #693
      - Use copy:, DVD (Box 9)
      - Streaming File:, 851831-B110-5.flv
    - Freedom and Education, 1962; [851831-B-110-6]; (University of Michigan faculty authorities discuss academic freedom and academic responsibility as fundamental conditions of a free society. Features: Nicholas Kazarinof UM-Math.; Jerold Israel, UM-Law; Stephen Tonsor, UM-Hist.; Elton McNeil)
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #386, Pos. #696
      - Streaming File:, 851831-B110-6.flv
    - Freedom and Segregation, 1962; [851831-B-110-7]; (University of Michigan faculty members consider progress and problems in the democratic achievement of personal freedom and equality for all American citizens. Features: Ralph Gibson, UM-Med; Sanford Kadish, UM-Law; Jerold Israel, UM-Law; Stephen Tonsor, UM-Hist.)
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #387, Pos. #700
      - Use copy:, DVD (Box 9)
      - Streaming File:, 851831-B110-7.flv
    - Freedom and Police Practices, 1962; [851831-B-110-8]; (University of Michigan law professors examine the democratic guarantees of personal freedom and the right to safety and security of the individual against arbitrary action by government enforcement agencies. Features: Jerold Israel, UM-Law; Sanford Kadish, UM-Law, Stephen Tonsor; Edmund Devine, UM-Law)
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #388, Pos. #728
      - Use copy:, DVD (Box 9)
      - Streaming File:, 851831-B110-8.flv
    - Freedom and Censorship, 1962; [851831-B-110-9]; (A novelist and UM faculty members analyze the modern restriction on the democratic free enterprise of ideas and the major ideas involved in the public and private censorship of books, magazines, films, etc. (print damaged) Features: Stephen Tonsor, UM-Hist.; Jerold Israel, UM-Law; Sanford Kadish, UM-Law; Earl Karr)
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #389, Pos. #920
    - Freedom and Conformity, 1962; [851831-B-110-10]; (Freedom and Conformity.; University of Michigan faculty authorities discuss the conflict between individual freedom and the American citizen's urgent search for security in a modern age of anxiety. Features: John Pollard, UM-Med.; Sanford Kadish, UM-Law; Jerold Israel, UM-Law; Stephen Tonsor, UM-Hist)
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #390, Pos. #729
      - Use copy:, DVD (Box 9)
      - Streaming File:, 851831-B110-10.flv
  - Law and the Man of Property, 1962; [851831-B-111]; (Two University of Michigan law professors offer a close and revealing study of the legal meaning of ownership in the modern world. Features: Richard V. Wellman, UM-Law; Joseph Julin, UM-Law)
    - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #385, Pos. #3168
  - Overseas American, The, 1962; [851831-B-112]; (A United States Information Agency instructor questions Peace Corps volunteers in training at the University of Michigan about the U.S. as he plays the role of well informed foreigners. Features: Charles Vetter)
    - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #391, Pos. #730
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 9)
    - Streaming File:, 851831-B112.flv
  - Top Women, The, 1962; [851831-B-113]; (Five top women business executives describe the difficulties of women in the business world in an informal panel discussion. Features: John A. Hanson, UM-Class.; Virginia Allen; Rita Bolitho; Nancy Roman, Hettie Smith)
    - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #394, Pos. #817
  - Ivan Goes to School, 1962-1963; [851831-B-114]; (A comparison is made between Russian and American systems of education by a University of Michigan professor of education and surprising similarities are pointed out. Features: William Medlin, UM-Ed.)
    - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #400, Pos. #822
  - Robert Frost, 1962-1963; [851831-B-115]; (A special film documentary on Frost's press conference and lecture at UM less than a year before he died. Frost reads his poem "Never Again Will Birds' Song Be the Same." [Sound quality is poor in some sections] Features: Robert Frost; Donald Hall)
    - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #401, Pos. #823
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 9)
  - From Rebel to Reformer, 1962; [851831-B-116]; (The development of the American woman from her underprivileged 19th century position to her active role in reform movements today is analyzed and illustrated. A suffragette is interviewed as are members of LWV, WCTU, Planned Parenthood, and HOME Features: Robert Blood, UM-Soc.; Mrs George C. Grimes)
    - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #404, Pos. #3008
  - Conflict: The Sentinels, 1963; [851831-B-117-4]; (The Sentinels; A discussion of the increasing scope and responsibilities of America's military establishment with experts who have unique experiences working with the military in civilian capacities. Features: Elton McNeil, UM-Psych.; James K. Pollock, UM-Pol.; David Singer, UM-ISMRD)
    - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #409, Pos. #760
  - Heads and/or Tails, 1963; [851831-B-118]; (Memory transfer and cannibalism in flatworms, training flatworms to run mazes. UM scientists will discuss some new ideas about the nature of learning and memory based upon experiments conducted with flatworms. Features: Elton B. McNeill, UM-Psych; James McConnel, UM-Psych; John Bardach, UM Zool.)
    - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #411, Pos. #845
  - Secretary of the Interior: Stewart Udall, 1962-1963; [851831-B-119]; (Sec. of the Interior Udall is interviewed by professors from the UM School of Natural Resources. Features: Stewart Udall; Stanley Cain, UM-SNR; Stephen Spurr, UM-SNR)
    - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #413, Pos. #848
  - Hard Work If You Can Get It, 1962-1963; [851831-B-120]; (Peace Corps Program Officers for the Far East and West Africa programs discuss the different roles the Peace Corps plays: in the lives of individual volunteers, in the countries in which they serve, and in the domestic life of the U.S. Features: Arthur Mendel, UM-Hist.; Harold G. Tufty; John D. Rockefeller IV)
    - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #416, Pos. #842
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 9)
    - Streaming File:, 851831-B120.flv
  - Perspective: Peace Corps, 1962-1963; [851831-B-121]; (Chief of Overseas Planning and Projects for the Peace Corps and UM history professor take a hard look at the Corps, past, present, and future. Features: Arthur Mendel, UM-Hist.; Warren Wiggins)
    - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #417, Pos. #483
  - Seventy Degrees South, 1962-1963; [851831-B-122]; (Swithinback, a leading Antarctic scientist and explorer will discuss the explorations and discoveries in Antarctica as well current studies and research. Features: Charles Swithinback, UM-IST; Charles Kelly, UM-Geol.)
    - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #418, Pos. #838
  - Sculpture from a Pump, 1962-1963; [851831-B-123]; (UM School of Architecture and Design faculty member and fountain designer discards concrete structure and creates sculptural shapes in water. Features: Richard Jennings, UM-Arch.; Charles O'Donnell, UM-Engl.)
    - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #419, Pos. #836
  - Beyond Form, 1962-1963; [851831-B-124]; (The works, thoughts, and philosophy of a world renowned architect, Walter Breuer, are discussed by Breuer and chairman of the UM Department of Architecture. Features: Walter Saunders, UM-Arch.; Walter Breuer)
    - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #420, Pos. #835
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 9)
    - Streaming File:
  - Through the Eyes of Children
    - Puppets and Puppeteers, 1962-1963; [851831-B-125]; (Puppets and Puppeteers; The famous Bixby marionettes of Saline, Michigan join storyteller Mary Ann Stevenson in portraying the tale of "Jack and the Beanstalk." A visit backstage to see how the puppeteers manipulate the marionettes. Features: Mary Ann Stevenson; Meredith Bixby)
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #427, Pos. #2630
  - Our Other Children, 1963-1964; [851831-B-126]; (A hopeful look at some grown-ups of tomorrow in the nation's inner city schools of today. Director of the Detroit chapter of the Great Cities Improvement Project discusses how the Project works with child, school and, community. Features: Henry Meyer, UM-SW; Carl Marburger)
    - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #432, Pos. #830
  - Report From Ann Arbor, 1963-1964; [851831-B-127]; (Harlan Hatcher, President of the University of Michigan describes his institution's present status to the people of the state. Features: Harlan Hatcher, UM-Pres.)
    - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #433, Pos. #832
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 9)
    - Streaming File:, 851831-B127.flv
  - Seatbelts for Survival, 1963-1964; [851831-B-128]; (The positive value of seatbelts are shown in a report of the research conducted by two UM Medical School professors. Features: Donald Huelke, UM-Med.; Paul Gikas, UM-Med.)
    - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #436, Pos. #853
  - Encounter
    - Automation and Society, 1963-1964; [851831-B-129-1]; (Automation and Society.;Experts from the University of Michigan Institute of Labor and Industrial Relations and Bureau of Industrial Relations discuss the problems posed to the nation by automation. Features: Hyman Kornbluh, UM-ILIR, George S. Odiorne, UM-BIR, Arthur Mendel, UM-Hist.)
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #446, Pos. #953
    - Armament/Disarmament, 1963-1964; [851831-B-129-2]; (Armament/Disarmament.; Political scientist and mathematical theorist present their views on the arms race and its place in world society. Features: Anatol Rapaport, UM-Math; Harold Jacobson, UM-Pol.; Arthur Mendel, UM-Hist.)
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #447, Pos. #952
    - Perception of Fear, 1963-1964; [851831-B-129-3]; (Perception of Fear.; Internationally known UM expert on game theory examines international relations and the value of "game theory" in planning national strategy. Features: Anatol Rapaport, UM-Math; Arthur Mendel UM-Hist.)
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #448, Pos. #951
    - Mass v. Excellence, 1963-1964; [851831-B-131-4]; (Mass v. Excellence.; Three UM scholars meet to debate "quality vs. quantity" in education, examining the pros and cons of establishing an intellectual elite. Features: Arnold S. Kaufman, UM-Phil.; Gerald F. Else, UM-Class.; Arthur Mendel, UM-Hist.)
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #452, Pos. #947
  - Report on Arms Control
    - Arms Control and Disarmament Agency, 1963-1964; [851831-B-130-1]; (Arms Control and Disarmament Agency.; Sen. Hubert Humphrey and staff members of the Arms Control and Disarmament Agency report on the founding of the agency, its mission, and the U.S. effort to ease world tension by planning for disarmament. Features: Elton B. McNeil, UM-Psych.; Hubert Humphrey; Thomas Lough; Bernard Bechoefer)
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #450, Pos. #949
    - An Effort from Many Quarters, 1963-1964; [851831-B-130-2]; (An Effort From Many Quarters.; Efforts to control weaponry are viewed by UM psychologist Elton B. McNeil and representatives from government, industry, and private peace research groups. Features: Elton B. McNeil, UM-Psych.;)
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #451, Pos. #948
  - Kennedy Years, The, 1963-1964; [851831-B-132]; (Four UM professors discuss and appraise the presidency of the late president John Fitzgerald Kennedy Features: Joseph Kallenback, UM-Law; Sanford Kadish, UM-Law; Bradford Perkins, UM-Hist; Arthur Eastman)
    - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #453, Pos. #938
  - Press Conference with Willard Wirtz, 1963-1964; [851831-B-133]; (U.S. Sec. of Labor discusses many significant labor issues of the 1960s during a press conference held on the UM campus. Features: Willard Wirtz, Sec. of Labor)
    - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #459, Pos. #945
  - Nine Days that Made America, 1963-1964; [851831-B-134]; (Story of nine critical days in the Revolution and Washington's successful response. Features: Howard Peckham)
    - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #460, Pos. #944
  - World of Work
    - Job of Choice, 1963-1964; [851831-B-135]; (Job Of Choice:; The guidance counselors role as he helps youths choose careers, some pressures involved, and what youths and parents can expect from counseling. Features: Edward Stasheff, UM-Speech; Delmont K. Byrn, UM-Ed.)
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #467, Pos. #933
  - Tuskegee, 1963-1964; [851831-B-136]; (The history, present educational aims, and future of Alabama's Tuskegee Institute. A discussion of the UM-Tuskegee cooperative exchange program and a performance by the Tuskegee choir. Features: N. Edd Miller, UM-VPAA; Russell Brown)
    - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #477, Pos. #1045
  - Film Maker and Critic, 1963-1964; [851831-B-137]; (A film critic and a film maker air their views on the role and problems of experimental film makers. A portion of an experimental film illustrates many of the points they discuss. Features: George Manupelli, UM-Art; Pauline Kael)
    - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #479, Pos. #1051
  - Point of Control, 1963-1964; [851831-B-138]; (Staff member of the UM Computing Center discusses how the computer works for us today and what it may make possible tomorrow. Features: Bernard Galler, UM)
    - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #484, Pos. #1989
  - Root and the Flower, The, 1963-1964; [851831-B-139]; (Editor of the Middle English Dictionary reports on its compilation at the University of Michigan. Features: John Reidy, UM-Engl.)
    - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #485, Pos. #929
  - Working Scientist, The, 1964-1965; [851831-B-140]; (A discussion of research results challenging the traditional picture of the creative scientist as a man off by himself, working in a specialized area and setting his own goals. Features: Frank M. Andrews, UM-ISR)
    - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #487, Pos. #927
  - Change and excellence
    - Change and excellence, 1964-1965; [851831-B-141]; (Change and Excellence.; A study of the problems facing administrators of large educational institutions who try to maintain academic quality. Features: N. Edd Miller, UM-Ed.; William Haber, UM-Econ.)
      - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #488, Pos. #919
  - Hopewell Heritage, 1964-1965; [851831-B-142]; (A study of an excavation into American prehistory and its significance. Including film of UM excavation of a Hopewell Indian site. Features: James B. Griffin, UM-Anthro.; Richard Flanders)
    - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #493, Pos. #1043
    - Use copy:, DVD (Box 9)
    - Streaming File:, 851831-B142.flv
  - Dance in Progress, 1964-1965; [851831-B-143]; (Dance instructor and composer, discuss creating and performing modern dance. Features: Elizabeth Weil; William Malm, UM-Music)
    - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #510, Pos. #1042, 2-inch video #765
  - Children Who Hate, 1964-1965; [851831-B-144]; (Training of people who work with emotionally disturbed kids, guidance and therapy at UM Fresh Air Camp. Features: Elton B. McNeill, UM-Psych.)
    - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #511, Pos. #665, 2-inch video #458
  - Civil Rights and Stained Glass Windows, 1964-1965; [851831-B-145]; (Dir. of UM Office of Religious Affairs leads a discussion of the clergy's place in the civil rights movement. Hawkins, United Presbyterian, looks at responsibility of black and white clergy. Dotson describes his 1964 voter registration work. Features: N. Patrick Murray, UM Off. Rel. Aff.; Elder G. Hawkins; Paul Dotson)
    - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #512, Pos. #1041
  - Return From Llanogrande, 1964-1965; [851831-B-146]; (Two Peace Corps volunteers tell of their experiences in a small Ecuadorian village. Features: Robert and Flo Griffen)
    - Original:, 16mm kinescope film, neg. #513, Pos. #1040
  - Vista for America, 1964-1965; [851831-B-147]; (A discussion of the objectives of V.I.S.T.A. (Volunteers in Service to America) the domestic Peace Corps with VISTA official Richard Gerson, a UM student volunteer, and a Detroit anti-poverty official. Features: William E. Porter, UM-Jour.; Richard Gerson)